dressupstyle.com 2014-04-01

# Privacy Policy

## Our Privacy Policy 

DressupStyle, its advertisers and affiliates are deeply committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users. Below is information outlining our continued support for the responsible management of consumer information. 

**Consumer Information**

During the process of delivering an ad to you, no personally identifiable information about you such as name, address, phone number, or e-mail address is collected. However, some types of non-personally identifiable information such as the Internet Service Provider you use to connect to the Internet, your browser type, or the type of computer operating system you use (Macintosh or Windows, for example) are obtained. The information collected are used for the purpose of targeting ads and measuring ad effectiveness on behalf of our advertisers. In some cases, you may voluntarily provide personal information in response to a specific ad (this ad may ask you to fill out a survey or provide your zip code). If this does occur, this information may be collected on behalf of an advertiser. This information is used by an advertiser to respond to your request. In addition, This information may be combined with other users' information and review it in an aggregate form to understand the type of individuals who view a specific type of ad or visit a particular kind of website. 

**Data Collection and Opt Out**

Ads shown on our site, as well as most sites on the Internet, use "cookies" to enhance your experience on the web. These cookies cannot be used to personally identify you in any way. What are cookies and why do we use them? A cookie is a unique number that is provided to you the first time an ad is served to you. This unique number, which is stored in a cookie file on your computer, helps target ads to you. This cookie can help ensure that the same ad will not be served you multiple times, and help our advertisers understand what you like and don't like about their offerings so that they can cater better to your needs the next time you are interested in their products or services. While we believe that cookies enhance your Internet experience by limiting the number of times you see the same ad and delivering more relevant content to you, they are not required for an ad to be delivered you. If you do not want the benefit of cookies, there is a simple procedure to manually delete your cookies. Please consult your web browser's Help documentation for more information. If you have any additional questions about DressupStyle's dedication to consumer privacy, please [contact us](http://www.dressupstyle.com/contact.php) with our form. 

**Advertisers**

This site, DressupStyle, uses the services of Yahoo, Google, MochiAds, CPM Star and ValueClick for the serving and/or targeting of ads, promotions and other marketing messages. To do this, they collect anonymous data through the use of cookies. Cookies reside on the browser dependant on the computer it saved on. 

  * To learn more about Google, go to <http://www.google.com/privacy.html>
  * To learn more about Casale Media, <http://www.casalemedia.com/privacy.html>
  * To learn more about CPM Star, <http://cpmstar.com/index.asp?nav=privacy>
  * To learn more about MochiAds, <https://www.mochiads.com/privacy.html>
  * To learn more about Yahoo, go to [http://privacy.yahoo.com](http://privacy.yahoo.com/)
  * To learn more about FastClick, go to <http://www.fastclick.com/about/opt-out.html>
  * To learn more about ValueClick, go to <http://www.valueclick.com/privacy.html>
